The dress doesn't hide my binder!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do I do now?!
There's no way I can take it off.
But I can't keep it on either...
Ashiya-kun.
Is the length okay?
Y-Yeah!
Looks like it's just right.
Okay.
So Ashiya-kun's dress is good.
I'll have to give up the binder...
You're finally—
Hey, looking cute!
Yikes!
Please let me survive this!
You really look like a girl.
I think it'll do.
These padded bras are really
nice though, huh?
Yeah, they are.
Hey. Your shoes.
Thanks, Sano.
You in charge of shoes?
They told me to help if I had the time.
Anyway, that dress...
It looks good on you.
He complimented me.
My ears are burning.
I'm so simple.
Mizuki-kun.
These are your stockings
for the actual dance.
Here you go.
Has something good happened, Kanna-chan?
What?
Can you tell?
Well, what is it?
Um, you see...
Yesterday, Megumi-sama asked me
to be his dance partner.
Good for you, Kanna-chan!
Nice going, gorilla boy!
Now, how should I put this?
I think you've got a real shot
at being crowned queen.
Schöne Fräulein!
Would you care to da—
Get lost.
Warum?!
Beautiful raven-haired miss,
would you care to...
Get your hands off of her!
Kanna is my fiancé!
What in the world?!
I'm So Happy!
So then, he goes and spills
the beans in front of everyone.
Tennoji was real uncomfortable after that.
I'm surprised she'd go
for a meathead like him.
Right?
So, tomorrow's the big day, huh?
Sure is.
H-Hey, uh, I was wondering if
I could ask you a favor.
I was hoping you'd dance with me...
Right now.
I really asked him!
Sure.
And a one and a two...
Th-Thanks!
I appreciate it!
I'm going to bed!
Good night!
I wasn't expecting that.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the time-honored
gathering of our two schools.
We hope you will enjoy
yourselves to the fullest.
Why is she the only one
who gets a special dress?
Talk about shady.
Hey.
Sano looks so freaking cool!
Mizuki's very, very cute!
SLAM
But seriously...
It looks really good on you.
The boobs are so real too.
That's because they are.
You look pretty sharp yourself.
Oh, wow!
It's like a real ball!
Senpai, I think we're in the wrong place.
I think so too.
Please dance with me.
With me!
Oh, what should I do?
Looks like someone feels
completely at home here.
There's Nanba-senpai!
He's as popular as ever.
Ten thousand points says
that that won't last long.
What do you mean?
Here it comes!
Senpai!
Told you.
I wonder where Sano got off to.
Hello, little lambs.
Schöner Abend.
Keep making those innocent little faces,
and the Big Bad Wolf
will eat you right up.
When you say it,
it doesn't sound like a joke.
You scared me!
Kujo-senpai!
Kadoma is my partner, so please
refrain from overstepping.
We're here, so want to try
a dance before the main event?
O-Osu!
You can't whip out the karate
stuff dressed like that.
Omigosh, it's Oscar-sama!
Schöne Fräulein.
Hey, there you are!
Mizuki-kun, I've been looking for you.
Rio-chan.
Where have you been?
You weren't in the changing room.
Sorry! I was in the toilet...
It's the only place I can change.
Kanna-chan gave this to me.
What?
Everyone's already wearing theirs,
but you weren't around, so...
Here.
All done!
That looks so good on you, Mizuki-kun!
You really look like a real girl!
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
Huh? Why?
That I got paired up with Sano.
Sorry, but I noticed.
My big brother's who he is, you know?
It's hard when the person you
have a crush on is too cool, huh?
Leaves you on pins and needles.
Huh?
I saw Sano-kun earlier.
The girls were swarming him,
so he had to keep running away.
Why am I not surprised?
I feel for you, Mizuki-kun.
But I understand these
kinds of things, so don't worry.
Um...
Good luck!
I'm rooting for you!
See you later!
Rio-chan, you're...
So the girls are flocking to him, huh?
Hey, Mizuki.
Here you are.
What's up? Yer lookin' blue.
Nakatsu?
Would you dance with me, princess?
Okay!
S-Still...
I know I shouldn't, but I keep staring!
Not my fault when they look so real!
Nakatsu.
Yes?!
Check it out.
Looks like Hibari-sama is dancing.
Oh, that girl with the big
boobs is going to dance too?
Oh no!
Now that I've noticed them,
I can't stop thinking about them!
Forget aboob it...
Boobs!
Nakatsu?!
Senpai, what's wrong?
Seeing how sexy Hibari-sama is
made him pass out or something.
Th-That's not it!
Is he going to be okay?
Mizuki-kun!
Oh no!
That's so awful!
Who would do such a thing?!
That's low.
Oh no. Poor thing...
Guess they got me.
Ashiya.
Sano...
This is terrible.
What happened?
It's terrible.
Someone ruined Mizuki-kun's dress.
It's fine, it's fine!
Rio-chan, I think I can wash it out.
I'll go give it a try.
Hey.
I don't want Sano to see me like this.
It's not coming out...
I won't cry, though.
Not over this.
How's it looking?
No luck, I'm afraid.
It is what it is.
Oh gosh.
Wow, you're right.
It's really stained now.
Mizuki-kun, will you let us
take care of this?
Huh?
S-Sure...
And now, the highlight of the night:
the dance where our king, queen,
and best couple will be chosen.
Yup, when it comes to crossdressing,
taking pictures is better than doing it!
I know didn't get a partner,
but why do I have to dance with Nakao?
I won't dance with any guy
other than Senpai!
Hey, I'm a guy too.
They fixed my dress for me,
but Nakatsu's gone too.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's finally the last dance!
I'm still here at the Christmas ball.
Might as well make the best of it
and enjoy things.
Ashiya...
If you're that worried
about him, go to him.
I'll be fine.
Plus, if you don't,
someone else might take him.
Sorry about this.
Sano?
Huh? Sano?
I'll dance with you.
Being a wallflower's no fun.
But...
It's okay! It's okay!
Go, go, go!
So, what do you say?
Or are you done with dancing?
I'd like to dance.
Me too.
Here we go.
Don't look away.
B-But...
But what?
It's embarrassing.
Dummy.
Relax.
It's just a dance.
Let's keep it easy.
Look.
How cute.
To me, you're a hundred times cuter!
Senpai, Senpai! Check it out!
They look so good!
You're going to get hurt
if you let your eyes wander.
Look at the hummingbird go.
We can't lose to them, Masao-san.
I feel the same.
I'll just have endure this one dance.
Just in order to showcase my
abilities to their fullest.
Hang in there, hang in there.
She just happens to be the only one
who can help me showcase my best.
Thank you all for your patience.
We will now announce this year's
winner based on the votes.
This doesn't concern us, so let's bail.
You said it.
We will begin by announcing our queen.
Do you mind waiting here for a sec?
Here you go.
What is this?
Tomorrow's your birthday, right?
I'm a day early, but it's
your birthday present.
It somehow slipped by last year,
so I swore I'd get it in this year.
I wanted to be the first
to wish you happy birthday.
Oh, snow!
Awesome!
It's snowing!
You're like a little kid.
But this is my first time seeing snow.
Real snow!
Really?
Really.
It's so cold!
Oh, it melted.
Ah!
You're going to catch a cold.
Happy birthday, Sano.
Thank you.
Looks like it's going to stick.
Want me to warm you up?
Senpai!
Akiha!
What are you doing here?
Let go!
Christmas is just around the corner.
Maybe I should stay over at your place?
Absolutely not.
Oh, wow, this is so nice.
Hey, wasn't that my present?
But it feels so good.
I'm a day early, but it's
your birthday present.
An ultrasonic massager!
This is so unsexy.
It was a bargain!
I got it pretty cheap!
Don't even worry about the price.
I told you, I'm happy you got it.
Thank you.
Calm down.
I need to calm down.
Julia
It's Julia.
Mizuki!
Wanna have some taiyaki with me?
Clingy
Hey.
Yay, I want some!
You know, the old me would've seen
this and just completely lost it,
but the new me is different.
I'm manning up to the max!
So as the super manly
Nakatsu-kun Revolution Type E,
Mizuki, your heart will beat for m—
How's it going, Julia?
Hi, Mizuki!
I'm doing great.
Listen, I was wondering how the
dance turned out for you.
Well, actually...
Hey. Been a while, American woman.
I see you're as annoying as ever,
you dumb ape.
How dare you?!
Hey, guys.
I got this coupon from my grandma.
Want to go skating?
Yeah!
That sounds like...
Hi, Julia.
It's been months since you left,
and you have no idea how lonely I've—
She hung up.
Don't just stand there!
Come over here, Nakatsu!
Y-Yeah...
Hey, that guy can't skate!
Ha ha!
You idiots!
When it comes to winter sports,
we Kansai folks ski or snowboard
in the Lake Biwa valley.
We can go skating blindfolded!
Being able to skate in that
position is a talent all its own.
Ashiya looks like he's having fun.
Like a fish in the water.
There's someone else taking
to this like a fish to water.
I knew I recognized you as
one of those PuPa models!
You look so good in real life!
I can't believe it.
Is that coat from the shoot?
He's resorting to cheap tricks, I see.
Senpai!
You said you'd skate with me.
You're such a bad boy.
W-We can't compete!
Let's go, Senpai.
So this is my life now...
Nakao's got a new strategy.
Smart play.
Efficient and he didn't hafta
sacrifice anything himself...
Hey, hey, what are you guys talking about?
Oh, yeah, Nakao-kun walks a hard road.
After all, he fell for the guy
who got crowned king.
That's right.
I thought Hibari-sama was overwhelming.
Absolutely!
It's no wonder she was crowned queen!
That's not what I meant.
Hibari-sama!
You know,
I'm convinced the voting was
rigged so only St. Blossom could win.
Yeah.
I thought Ashiya was cuter.
A rival!
What are you talking about, Kayashima?
I mean, look at yourselves.
You two won the special
award for best couple.
Oh, yeah!
I never thought Sano and I would
win an award together!
But it's not like that's
super official or anything.
The real best couple was
Tennoji and Kanna-chan.
I'm such a loser!
If only I hadn't passed out back then!
The best couple would've
been me and Mizuki!
Dumdum.
Kyomi?
What are you doing here?
Hey! I told you to not run off!
Kagurazaka?
Look at you, being a good big brother.
The hell are you talking about?
Onii-chan!
Tamami-chan!
Haven't seen you in forever!
From Tokyo High School?
Yeah.
What a coincidence, Mizuki-kun.
Izumi-sama, you're going
for the next meet, right?
I'll be cheering for you!
Later!
Sano, you better not get some lame score.
Of course not.
Let's go.
Kyomi.
High five!
Wait.
Those are Rio-chan's parents!
Oh my!
Are you two on a date?
That's right!
The coupon expires today.
Wait, those two are
Doctor Umeda's parents?
They're in their fifties. Just sayin'.
Nanba-senpai, wait for me!
Wait a second.
That long-haired cutie is Minami-chan!
Oh, fancy running into you,
Granma and Granpa...
Granma? Granpa?
He's their grandson?!
Then that means Io is...
Mother & Son
Umeda is...
Uncle & Nephew
Rio-chan is...
Aunt & Nephew
What's up?
What's going on?
What's going on is that
Rio-chan is Nanba's aunt.
Rio-chan, I'm so sorry!
What? Rio-chan is his aunt?!
It got out!
Aunt? His aunt?!
Oh, you, Minami-chan!
I've told you so many times to just
call us Mama Seira and Papa Azuma!
Seira.
Come to me.
Squee!
Azuma-chan!
Th-Thanks for that...
By the way,
they won the best couple award
at the joint ball in their day.
Whoever gets voted best couple
supposedly lives happily ever after.
Seeing them together, I can't just
write it off as superstition.
That was close.
Thank you.
Be careful.
It's really slippery at
the edge of the rink.
Let's go skate.
Hey! Don't leave me behind!
Maybe a little of the
superstition will rub off.
We did win best couple, after all.
I'm so happy right now.
May Sano and I always be together!